cloudlinux.com 2019-05-07

# CloudLinux - Privacy Policy

**CLOUD LINUX Inc.** is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy applies to those who visit cloudlinux.com, kernelcare.com, imunify360.com, cloudlinuxbackup.com, elasticsites.com and subdomains of those domains (“Site” or collectively “Sites”), as well as users of CloudLinux OS, KernelCare, Imunify360 and CloudLinux Backup software and services (“Service” or collectively “Services”) which is owned and operated by CLOUD LINUX INC. ("CLOUDLINUX", “We”, “Us” or “Our”). This privacy policy describes how CLOUDLINUX collects, uses and shares the personal information you provide to us. It also describes the choices available to you regarding the use of, your access to, and how to update and correct your personal information. The use of information collected through our products and services shall be limited to the purpose of providing the products and services for which our customer has contracted with CLOUDLINUX.  

### What information do we collect?

**Personal Information.  
** CLOUDLINUX may collect personally identifiable information from you such as names, addresses, telephone numbers, fax numbers, physical addresses, email addresses, credit card number (in the case of direct customers) and, if applicable, company names, addresses, telephone numbers, fax numbers, physical addresses, email addresses, credit card numbers or tax ID numbers as well as similar information concerning technical contacts, marketing contacts, and executive contacts within your company or organization (collectively, “Personal Information”).

**Non-Personal Information.  
** CLOUDLINUX may collect non-personally identifiable information from you such as the type of browser you use, your operating system, the screen resolution of your browser, your ISP, your IP address, which pages you view on the Site and the time and duration of your visits to the Site (collectively, “Non-Personal Information”).  CLOUDLINUX associates Non-Personal Information with Personal Information if you register with the Site.

**User Communications**.  
If you communicate with us, we may collect information relating to that communication whether it takes the form of email, fax, letter, forum posting, testimonials or any other form of communication between you and CLOUDLINUX or Submitted by you to the Site (collectively, “User Communications”).

**Server Information**.  
If you use one of our software products such as CloudLinux OS, KernelCare, Imunify360 or CloudLinux Backup, we may collect certain information concerning such software, its use, and concerning the server upon which the software operates.  This information includes: (a) the licensed or unlicensed status of the software; (b) the source from which the license for the software was obtained (CloudLinux or CloudLinux reseller or partner); or (c) information about the server upon which the software is installed including (i) the public IP address, (ii) the operating system and (iii) the use of any virtualization technologies on such server ((a) through (c) collectively, “Server Information”), server uptime and server hardware information including CPU, memory, disks, motherboard. Additionally, “Server Information” may also include (x) information collected by CloudLinux from time to time concerning which features of the software are most often used in order to improve and make adjustments to the software; and (y) information collected from you by CloudLinux in the event that you request technical support services including without limitation, IP addresses, usernames and passwords necessary to login to SSH, list of running processes and content of configuration files.

**Information about your customers (Imunify360).  
** Only if you use Imunify360, Imunify360 collects information about visitors of any site hosted on a server protected by Imunify360. That information includes visitors IP addresses, URI, browser information, screen resolution as well as other location & browser metadata. We might also collect HTTP/HTTPs query parameters, encrypted using one-way encryption (irreversible encryption used for comparison & analysis). If an attack is detected, we will collect HTTP parameters without using one-way encryption. We will still encrypt it for the purpose of transferring it to our servers.

**The content of your servers (CloudLinux Backup).  
** If you are using CloudLinux Backup, we back up your data to cloud servers, as specified by your backup settings.  Such backups may include a transfer of such data to approved locations in accordance with any Data Processing Agreement you have entered with CloudLinux.

### What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * **To improve customer service**
    * In the context of customer support, your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests.
  * **To process transactions**
    * Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * **To send periodic emails**
    * The email address you provide in the application may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your usage, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
  * **The data collected by Imunify360 about visitors is used to provide better security for Imunify360**
  * **The data backed up by CloudLinux Backup is used to analyze, improve, and provide our backup services**

### How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive information is transmitted via Transport Layer Security (TLS) technology to and then stored into our database to be only accessed by those authorized with special access rights to our systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. Credit card information is transmitted directly to the payment processor and is not stored on our servers. If you have any questions about the security of your personal information, you can contact us at [privacy@cloudlinux.com](mailto:privacy@cloudlinux.com). 

### Cookies or other tracking technologies?

Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

CLOUDLINUX uses cookies or similar technologies to analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. You can control the use of cookies at the individual browser level, but if you choose to disable cookies, it may limit your use of certain features or functions on our website or service.

**Log files.**

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically. This information may include Internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our site (e.g., HTML pages, graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, and/or clickstream data to analyze trends in the aggregate and administer the site.

**Behavioral Targeting.**

We partner with a third party to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use cookies or similar technologies in order to provide you advertising based upon your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to opt out of interest-based advertising click [here](http://preferences-mgr.truste.com/) (or if located in the European Union click [here](http://www.youronlinechoices.eu/)). Please note you will continue to receive generic ads.

### Do we share any information with outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personal information. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy policy. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

  * **Service Providers**
    * We may provide your personal information to companies that provide services to help us with our business activities such as offering customer service or processing your payment. These companies are authorized to use your personal information only as necessary to provide these services to us.
  * **With Your Consent**
    * We share information about you with third parties when you give us consent to do so.  For example, we often display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our public websites. With your consent, we may post your name alongside the testimonial.
  * **Third-Party Widgets**
    * Our blogs and forums might contain widgets and social media features, such as the Twitter "tweet" or Facebook "like" buttons. These widgets and features may collect your IP address, which page you are visiting on the Sites or Services, and may set a cookie to enable the feature to function properly. Widgets and social media features are either hosted by a third party or hosted directly on our Services. Your interactions with these features are governed by the privacy policy of the company providing it.
  * **Legal Disclaimer**
    * We may also disclose your personal information as required by law, such as to comply with a subpoena or similar legal process when we believe in good faith that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights, protect your safety or the safety of others, investigate fraud, or respond to a government request.

    * In the event CLOUDLINUX is involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our website, of any change in ownership, uses of your personal information, and choices you may have regarding your personal information.

    * We may also disclose your personal information to any other third party with your prior consent.

### User Access and Choice

Upon request, CLOUDLINUX will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your personal information. You may access, correct or request deletion of your personal information by logging in to your account or by contacting us at [[privacy@cloudlinux.com](mailto:privacy@cloudlinux.com).](https://www.cloudlinux.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#c1b1b3a8b7a0a2b881a2adaeb4a5ada8afb4b9efa2aeacef) We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe.

  * **Data Retention**
    * We will retain your information as needed to provide you services. Even if you close your account with CLOUDLINUX, we will still retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. However, we will identify your account in our database as “deleted” or “closed”.
  * **Opt-out Preferences**
    * When you register for an account, we will use your name and email address to send periodic emails to you of both promotional and transactional in nature. Out of respect for your privacy, you may choose to stop receiving promotional emails by following the unsubscribe instructions included in these emails or you can contact us at [privacy@cloudlinux.com](mailto:privacy@cloudlinux.com)[.](https://www.cloudlinux.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#6a1a18031c0b09132a0906051f0e0603041f124409050744)

We will also send you service-related email announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. You do not have an option to opt out of these emails, which are not promotional in nature.

###    
Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include links to our merchant partners (third party products or services) on our Sites. These third party’s websites have separate and independent privacy policies. We, therefore, have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked websites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our Sites and welcome any feedback about these third party websites.

  * **Testimonials**
    * We display personal testimonials of satisfied customers on our Sites in addition to other endorsements. With your consent, we may post your testimonial along with your name. If you wish to update or delete your testimonial, you can contact us at [privacy@cloudlinux.com](mailto:privacy@cloudlinux.com)
  * [](https://www.cloudlinux.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#49393b203f282a30092a25263c2d2520273c31672a2624)**Social Media Widgets:**
    * CloudLinux Sites may include links that direct you to other websites or services whose privacy practices may differ from ours. Your use of and any information you submit to any of those third-party sites is governed by their privacy policies, not this one.

###    
Consent to Our Terms and Conditions

Please also visit our Terms and Conditions section establishing your consent to the use, disclaimers, and limitations of liability governing the use of this Site.

Information Related to Data Collected through our Products and Services

  * **Information Related to Data Processor or Collected for our Customers:**
    * CloudLinux is considered a processor or sub-processor under the direction of our customers who are considered controllers or processors. CloudLinux has entered appropriate Data Processing Agreements with our customers controlling protection of your personal data.
  * ******Transfer of Personal Data to Third Parties:  
**** **
    * We may transfer personal data to third-party processor companies (i.e. cloud data and server services) that help us provide our service. Such third party processors are located in, and the transfers are limited to, the United States or countries in the European Union and these processors are controlled by data processing agreements providing the same protections of your personal data.
  * **Access and Retention of Data Controlled by our Customers:**
    * CloudLinux acknowledges that you have the right to access your personal information or ask for its removal. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct his/her query to the CloudLinux's customer (the data controller). If requested to remove data we will respond within a reasonable timeframe.
    * CloudLinux will retain personal data we process on behalf of our customers for as long as needed to provide Services to our customer. CloudLinux will also retain personal data as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

###    
Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to this [Privacy Policy](https://cloudlinux.com/privacy-policy).

###    
Changes to our Privacy Policy

We may update this Privacy Policy to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the e-mail address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

### INTERNATIONAL DATA TRANSFERS:

Cloud Linux Inc. complies with the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework and the Swiss – U.S. Privacy Shield Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union and Switzerland to the United States, respectively. Cloud Linux Inc has certified to the Department of Commerce that it adheres to the Privacy Shield Principles. If there is any conflict between the terms in this privacy policy and the Privacy Shield Principles, the Privacy Shield Principles shall govern. To learn more about the Privacy Shield program, and to view our certification, please visit <https://www.privacyshield.gov/>[.](https://www.privacyshield.gov/)

[](https://www.privacyshield.gov/)With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Frameworks, Cloud Linux is subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.

Pursuant to the Privacy Shield Frameworks, EU and Swiss individuals have the right to obtain our confirmation of whether we maintain personal information relating to you in the United States. Upon request, we will provide you with access to the personal information that we hold about you. You may also may correct, amend, or delete the personal information we hold about you. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data transferred to the United States under Privacy Shield, should direct their query to [[privacy@cloudlinux.com](mailto:privacy@cloudlinux.com).](https://www.cloudlinux.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#e696948f9087859fa6858a8993828a8f88939ec885898bc8) If requested to remove data, we will respond within a reasonable timeframe.

We will provide an individual opt-out or opt-in choice before we share your data with third parties other than our agents, or before we use it for a purpose other than which it was originally collected or subsequently authorized. To request to limit the use and disclosure of your personal information, please submit a written request to [privacy@cloudlinux.com](mailto:privacy@cloudlinux.com)[.](https://www.cloudlinux.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#bbcbc9d2cddad8c2fbd8d7d4cedfd7d2d5cec395d8d4d695)

[](https://www.cloudlinux.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#bcccced5cadddfc5fcdfd0d3c9d8d0d5d2c9c492dfd3d192)In certain situations, we may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements.

Cloud Linux’s accountability for personal data that it receives in the United States under the Privacy Shield and subsequently transfers to a third party is described in the Privacy Shield Principles. In particular, Cloud Linux remains responsible and liable under the Privacy Shield Principles if third-party agents that it engages to process the personal data on its behalf do so in a manner inconsistent with the Principles, unless Cloud Linux proves that it is not responsible for the event giving rise to the damage.

In compliance with the Privacy Shield Principles, Cloud Linux commits to resolve complaints about your privacy and our collection or use of your personal information transferred to the United States pursuant to Privacy Shield. European Union and Swiss individuals with Privacy Shield inquiries or complaints should first contact BILT by email at [[privacy@cloudlinux.com](mailto:privacy@cloudlinux.com).](https://www.cloudlinux.com/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection#9ceceef5eafdffe5dcfff0f3e9f8f0f5f2e9e4b2fff3f1b2)

ACCESSING OR USING OUR SITES OR SERVICES, OR OTHERWISE PROVIDING INFORMATION TO US OR OUR CUSTOMERS, CONSTITUTES CONSENTING TO OUR POTENTIAL TRANSFER, PROCESSING AND STORAGE OF SUCH INFORMATION IN THE UNITED STATES.

### Dispute Resolution

Within the scope of this privacy notice, if a privacy complaint or dispute cannot be resolved through Cloud Linux Inc’s internal processes, Cloud Linux Inc has agreed to participate in the VeraSafe Privacy Shield Dispute Resolution Procedure. Subject to the terms of the VeraSafe Privacy Shield Dispute Resolution Procedure, VeraSafe will provide appropriate recourse free of charge to you. To file a complaint with VeraSafe under the Privacy Shield Dispute Resolution Procedure, please submit the required information to VeraSafe here: <https://www.verasafe.com/privacy-services/dispute-resolution/submit-dispute/>.

If your Privacy Shield complaint cannot be resolved through the above channels, under certain conditions, you may invoke binding arbitration for some residual claims not resolved by other redress mechanisms. See Privacy Shield Annex 1 at <https://www.privacyshield.gov/article?id=ANNEX-I-introduction>.

### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Site or your dealings with this Site, you may contact us using the information below:

**Cloud Linux Inc**  
2318 Louis Rd, Suite B  
Palo Alto, CA 94303, USA
